https://www.justdiplomaframes.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES JUST DIPLOMA FRAMES COLLECT?
You are free to come to Just Diploma Frames and browse through the site’s offerings. We will only ask for personal information when you order your frame.
A WORD ABOUT “COOKIES”
Cookies are small bits of data used by Just Diploma Frames to enhance the site’s functionality and make your shopping experience easier and more personalized. Cookies are also used specifically to enable the site’s online shopping features. Your browser must accept cookies if you want to add products to your online shopping cart or to purchase the products online. If your browser does not support cookies, you can place orders by calling 1-801-243-9218.
HOW DOES JUST DIPLOMA FRAMES USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the personal information you provide to fill your orders, to personalize the site, to provide customer service assistance and to improve the content of our site so that we can better meet your needs. We will e-mail our customers regarding order status, and customer service issues.
WILL PERSONAL INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH OUTSIDE ENTITIES?
No. Just Diploma Frames will use the information you provide us for internal purposes only. We will not sell, rent or trade the information to any outside entity.
HOW IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION PROTECTED FROM THEFT?
Just Diploma Frames uses SSL (Secure Socket Layers) encryption technology, the standard for ensuring secure data transmission across the Internet. SSL ensures that the data you provide us can only be read by Just Diploma Frames servers. When you purchase an item from us, your credit card number is stored in a location that is not accessible to the Internet. Because of the importance we place on security, your browser must support SSL for you to participate in any of the site’s interactive functions, including online purchasing. If your browser does not support SSL, you can place orders by calling 1-801-243-9218. If you feel uncomfortable sending your credit card information over the Web, you can call us at 801-243-9218 to complete your order.
